[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
        "optionA": "Dog",
        "optionB": "Elephant",
        "optionC": "Goat",
        "optionD": "Lion",
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which country operationalized world’s largest radio telescope?",
        "optionA": "USA",
        "optionB": "China",
        "optionC": "Russia",
        "optionD": "India",
        "answer": "China"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which one among the following radiations carries maximum energy?",
        "optionA": "Ultraviolet rays",
        "optionB": "Gamma rays",
        "optionC": "X- rays",
        "optionD": "Infra-red rays",
        "answer": "Gamma"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is India’s rank on the WEF’s Global Social Mobility Index 2020?",
        "optionA": "75",
        "optionB": "76",
        "optionC": "77",
        "optionD": "78",
        "answer": "76"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is",
        "optionA": "Silver",
        "optionB": "Zinc",
        "optionC": "Coppper",
        "optionD": "Gold",
        "answer": "Silver"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Who is the father of geometry?",
        "optionA": "Aristotle",
        "optionB": "Euclid",
        "optionC": "Pythagoras",
        "optionD": "Kepler",
        "answer": "Euclid"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "The World Largest desert is ?",
        "optionA": "Thar",
        "optionB": "Kalahari",
        "optionC": "Sahara",
        "optionD": "Sonoran",
        "answer": "Sahara"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Country that has the highest in Barley Production ?",
        "optionA": "China",
        "optionB": "India",
        "optionC": "Russia",
        "optionD": "France",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Country that was called as Land of Rising Sun ?",
        "optionA": "Russia",
        "optionB": "Japan",
        "optionC": "Holland",
        "optionD": "Korea",
        "answer": "Japan"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
        "optionA": "Dog",
        "optionB": "Elephant",
        "optionC": "Goat",
        "optionD": "Lion",
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
        "optionA": "Dog",
        "optionB": "Elephant",
        "optionC": "Goat",
        "optionD": "Lion",
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "id":12,
        "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
        "optionA": "Dog",
        "optionB": "Elephant",
        "optionC": "Goat",
        "optionD": "Lion",
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
        "optionA": "Dog",
        "optionB": "Elephant",
        "optionC": "Goat",
        "optionD": "Lion",
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
        "optionA": "Dog",
        "optionB": "Elephant",
        "optionC": "Goat",
        "optionD": "Lion",
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
        "optionA": "Dog",
        "optionB": "Elephant",
        "optionC": "Goat",
        "optionD": "Lion",
        "answer": "Elephant"
    }
]